https://www.mbabadminton.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footerWho we areWe are Medway Badminton Association LtdOur website address is: https://www.mbabadminton.co.uk/What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsWhen you submit a contact form, your name, email, message and IP address will be sent to the person you elected to contact.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withWe do not currently use any 3rd party analytics on our siteHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your contact informationShould you have any questions about the use of your information, please contact our office.Primary SidebarUpcoming Events
Dec
11
Pay and Play — This is our family evening. At present the Government Guidelines and those of Badminton England...
Dec
15
Tipping The Balance — Tipping The Balance badminton sessions are held Tuesday mornings from 10am – 11.30am, £3 each....
Dec
16
St Matthews Club — Contact: Mike O’Keeffe Runs Wednesdays, 7pm-11pm
Dec
17
Ravel Club — Contact Richard Nash Meets Thursdays, 8pm-11pm
Dec
18
Pay and Play — This is our family evening. At present the Government Guidelines and those of Badminton England...Search this websiteUseful LinksFacebook Medway Badminton AssociationMedway Junior BadmintonKent Badminton Limited
National/County Badminton Badminton EnglandKent Badminton LimitedKent RegionsNorth Foreland Badminton AssociationSouth Foreland Badminton AssociationRainham & District Badminton LeagueTunbridge Wells Badminton LeagueRavensbourne Badminton AssociationOrpington&North West Kent Badminton Association
Other LinksIn partnership with Karakal UKCarlton SportsMedway Gets ActiveFooterEvent CategoriesGeneralJuniorsLadiesLeague ClubsRecent News
AGM Memoranda and article changes proposed
Company Accounts 2019 / 2020
Anyone recognise the stunner with the Red hair in the video?? Please do share a comment below.Opening HoursMonday to Friday – 10:00 to 23:00Saturday – 09:00 to 15:00 (Juniors only)Sunday – 19:00 to 22:30
Please note: There is currently no wheelchair access to this building.Contact UsCastlemaine Hall
100 Castlemaine Avenue
Gillingham, Kent
ME7 2QETel: 01634 572187Email: Click here to email us
